[
  {
    "question": "Which language is used for creating Web Pages?",
    "choice1": "PASCAL",
    "choice2": "C",
    "choice3": "HTML",
    "choice4": "BASIC",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "The communication protocol used by the Internet to transfer hypertext documents is",
    "choice1": "Hyper Text Internet Protocol",
    "choice2": "Hyper Text Transfer Protocol",
    "choice3": "Internet protocol",
    "choice4": "File Transfer Protocol",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "The entire web document is contained within ?",
    "choice1": "Comments",
    "choice2": "Tags",
    "choice3": "Web page",
    "choice4": "HTML element",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "HTML document should begin with the ?",
    "choice1": "<HEAD> tag",
    "choice2": "<TITLE> tag",
    "choice3": "<BODY> tag",
    "choice4": "<HTML> tag",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "The HTML and HTTP standard are defined by ?",
    "choice1": "Web client",
    "choice2": "Internet association",
    "choice3": "WWW consortium",
    "choice4": "WWW",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "GIF is the abbreviation of ?",
    "choice1": "Graphics Interchange Format",
    "choice2": "Graphics Instruction Format",
    "choice3": "Graphics Item Format",
    "choice4": "Graphics Information Format",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "The <Font> tag is similar to ?",
    "choice1": "<BIG>tag",
    "choice2": "<SMALL>tag",
    "choice3": "<MARQUEE>tag",
    "choice4": "<BIG>and<Small> tags",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the location address of the hypertext documents?",
    "choice1": "Uniform Resource Locator",
    "choice2": "Web server",
    "choice3": "File",
    "choice4": "Web address",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "The ____ passes the information given by the user to a specified program",
    "choice1": "User",
    "choice2": "Programmer",
    "choice3": "Web server",
    "choice4": "Browser",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is used to store the data within the documents on the server",
    "choice1": "XML",
    "choice2": "HTML",
    "choice3": "DHTML",
    "choice4": "CGI",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Web page editors works on a ____ principle",
    "choice1": "WWW",
    "choice2": "HTML",
    "choice3": "WYSIWYG",
    "choice4": "WYGWYSI",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which program is used by web clients to view the web pages?",
    "choice1": "Web browser",
    "choice2": "Protocol",
    "choice3": "Web server",
    "choice4": "Search Engine",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which tag is used to display text in title bar of a web document?",
    "choice1": "Body tag",
    "choice2": "Title tag",
    "choice3": "Meta tag",
    "choice4": "Comment tag",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What are shared on the Internet and are called as Web pages?",
    "choice1": "Programs",
    "choice2": "Cables",
    "choice3": "Hypertext documents",
    "choice4": "Content",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Transferring your HTML code from one machine to server is known as",
    "choice1": "Hosting",
    "choice2": "Indexing",
    "choice3": "Serving",
    "choice4": "Sorting",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "The ____ attribute is used to identify the values of variables",
    "choice1": "text",
    "choice2": "http-equiv",
    "choice3": "content",
    "choice4": "name",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "The tag used to add images to the HTML document is ?",
    "choice1": "<FONT>",
    "choice2": "<HR>",
    "choice3": "<HI>",
    "choice4": "<IMG>",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is a collection of controls in HTML",
    "choice1": "Form",
    "choice2": "Field",
    "choice3": "Table",
    "choice4": "Frame",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which are used with a tag to modify its function?",
    "choice1": "Files",
    "choice2": "Attributes",
    "choice3": "Functions",
    "choice4": "Documents",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the formal description of message formats and rules to be followed by computers?",
    "choice1": "Standards",
    "choice2": "Protocol",
    "choice3": "Syntax",
    "choice4": "Language",
    "answer": 2
  }
]